tollywood123.com 2017-12-17

# TOLLYWOOD

### Privacy Policy

Welcome to Tollywood.Net. We value your privacy, and want you to know what information we collect and what we do with it. From time to time, we may make changes to this Policy. We will endeavor to post the changes before they become effective. The effective date of the most recent version of the privacy policy will appear at the top of this page. This consumer privacy policy applies to any information we collect or receive about you, from any source

**Automatic Data Collection**

Cookies. We use a software technology called "cookies" for several purposes, depending on the type of cookie employed. Within Tollywood.net, we use what are commonly called "session" cookies, meaning that they only last as long as you are online. We use these cookies to identify you as a valid subscriber so that we can deliver music to you, to ensure that no one else can sign on simultaneously with your account from another computer and to help us personalize your service experience based on your registration preferences (such as genre). We may also use session cookies to help us facilitate any promotions or surveys that we provide. As part of the sign-in process, we may also use what are commonly called "persistent" cookies which stay with you after your session is over and you are offline. We only use these cookies in connection with a sign-in feature that allows you to save your member name and password so that the next time you sign in, these fields will be prepopulated for you. This cookie is only offered in conjunction with certain Affiliate Sites that choose to make it available and it can only be activated if you select that option during your sign-in. If you select this option you can always deselect it each time you sign-in. 

Other. In order to personalize our service for your enjoyment and to monitor and improve the performance of our technology, we do collect/capture other data such as a member's searches (such as their search criteria and results) and the music they listened to. We only share search history or music usage data on an aggregate basis. 

For our internal purposes, we gather information such as date, time, connection speed and IP address of all visitors to our site. We keep this information simply for our internal security audit log, trend analysis, and system administration. 

**Advertisers**

We work with various third party advertising networks. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by advertising network, and we do not have access to this information.

**Security**

Tollywood.net endeavors to protect the security of your personal information and your choices for its intended use. We use secure SSL technology to protect the transmission of sensitive information such as your registration, login, and credit card information. 

We store your personal information on a secure server, and use special procedures designed to protect the information we collect from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction. 

**Links**

We may display links to other sites within Tollywood.net. We are not responsible for those other sites, their privacy policies or how they treat information about their members. We advise you to check their privacy policies to find out how they are treating your personal information. 

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us.
